Guide to the Donald Davie Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- June 2013 Acquisition, 1940-2005; 12.88; (13 boxes)
  - Reviews, typescripts, manuscripts, clippings, and notes, 1961-1995 (Box 36)
  - Printed material, 1955-1995 (Box 37)
    Contains extensive marginalia, as well as ephemera.
  - Printed material, 1940-1986 (Box 38)
  - Printed material, 1953-2005 (Box 39)
  - Printed material, 1952-1984 (Box 40)
  - Printed material, 1952-1996 (Box 41)
  - Posters and broadsides, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 42 (Oversize))
  - Certificates, citations, and pencil drawing of Ezra Pound by Julie B., 1973-1982 (Box 43)
  - "Ezra Pound in Italy," slides, undated; 31 slides (Box 44)
  - Audiovisual material, circa 1970s-1990s; 5 VHS tapes, 2 reel-to-reels, and 26 audio cassettes.
    Box 45 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Donald Davie, interview by John Barrett, 1968-04; 1 (Box 45)
    - Friends of the Library Banquet, USC, 3 3/4 I.P.S., 1/2 Track, Helen Keller Tribute, 1969-03-23; 1 (Box 45)
    - Donald Davie, Poet as Sculptor, 1989-07-25; 1 (Box 45)
    - Polaris Entertainment: Donald Davie, Poet as Sculptor, circa 1989; 1 (Box 45)
    - Donald Davie, Poet as Sculptor, circa 1989; 1 (Box 45)
    - Polaris Entertainment, Inc.: "Donald Davie: Poet as Sculptor", 1989-01-10; 1 (Box 45)
    - Polaris Entertainment, Inc.: Donald Davie: "Poet as Sculptor", circa 1989; 1 (Box 45)
    - Memorial Lecture, Bristol University, "Atrocities and 'Christian Poetry'", 1990-03-20; 1 (Box 45)
    - Donald Davie, To Scorch or Freeze, 1998; 1 (Box 45)
    - Donald Davie: Selected Poems, 1985; 3 (Box 45)
    - "Time Passing, Beloved" (and others) Music: Alan MacDonald, undated; 1 (Box 45)
    - Donald Davie: Poet of the Month, 1990-05; 1 (Box 45)
    - Czeslaw Milosz, Lyubomir Nikolov: Poet of the Month, undated; 1 (Box 45)
    - Donald Davie + Carl Rakosi, 1988-04-27; 1 (Box 45)
    - Carl Rakosi (continued), 1987-06-30; 1 (Box 45)
    - Conversations with Donald Davie I, 1995-07-07; 1 (Box 45)
    - Conversations with Donald Davie II, 1995-07-07; 1 (Box 45)
    - Charles Tomlinson reads The Waste Land by T.S. Eliot, 1989-04-11; 1 (Box 45)
    - D. D. Critic, Poet & Teacher Cont., 1976; 1 (Box 45)
    - Poet of the Month: Ted Hughes, 1992-04; 1 (Box 45)
    - 'Sunday', 1995-09-24; 1 (Box 45)
    - Robert Allen, "Innocent Stranger", 1986-05-17; 1 (Box 45)
    - Roy Fuller: "These the Companions", 1982-04-08; 1 (Box 45)
    - Davie letter & 'Coo' (Rose-Marie) / Warsaw Concierto, undated; 1 (Box 45)
    - "Sunday Radio" Tribute to Donald Davie, 1995-04-24; 1 (Box 45)
    - William Barnes, 1986; 1 (Box 45)
    - Englands of the Mind, 1990-07-26; 1 (Box 45)
    - Every Poem an Epitaph (T.S. Eliot). Overseas Service, undated; 1 (Box 45)
    - Poet of the Month - Donald Davie - Complete, undated; 1 (Box 45)
    - To Scorch or Freeze, Donald Davie, 1988; 1 (Box 45)
    - Poets of the '50s: Larkin & Hughes, by Donald Davie & T. Paulin, 1990-07-26; 1 (Box 45)